Guide to the Vassar College Dean of Studies Records, 1867-2016
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Vassar College Dean of Studies Records
1867-2016
Vassar College. Dean of Studies
996.2 cubic feet (999 boxes)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Contains records related to student admissions, academic progress, grades, graduation, scholarships, fellowships, special academic programs, graduate students, and academic withdrawals.
Administrative History
Officially established in 1962 when the Dean of the College position was divided into the Dean of the Faculty and the Dean of Studies, the Dean of Studies office executes educational policies as they relate to students and enforces faculty legislation regarding requirements for degrees.
Scope and Content Note
The collection contains records related to student admissions, academic progress, class enrollment, grades, graduation, scholarships, fellowships, special academic programs, graduate students, and academic withdrawals.
Arrangement
Organized into two series: Series I. Student Records, 1867-2016; and Series II. Administrative Records, undated.
Access
Records of the Dean of Studies are restricted to College use only.
Related Materials
Vassar College Board of Trustees Records
Vassar College Dean of Students Records
.
Vassar College Registrar Records
.
Subject Headings
Organizations:
Vassar College--Administration; Vassar College--Students
Subjects:
Women college students--New York (State)--Poughkeepsiee; Women's colleges--New York (State)--Poughkeepsie)
Places:
Poughkeepsie (N.Y.)--History
VCL Categories:
Vassar College Administrative Offices and Functions
Encoding Information
Encoded by Emma Gronbeck, November 2023.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Office of the Dean of Studies in multiple accessions, 2005-2023. [A2006-028, A2006-029, A2007-034, A2008-024, A2008-033, A2009-036, A2010-018, A2010-023, A2011-041, A2011-042, A2012-021, A2013-040, A2014-006, A2014-017, A2014-038, A2014-039, A2015-007, A2015-011, A2016-025, A2017-010, A2017-019, A2017-020, A2018-009, A2019-049, A2019-072, A2020-011, A2021-029, A2022-009, A2023-042]
Series List
- Series I. Student Records, 1867-2016; (920 boxes) [RESTRICTED]
  - Subseries A. General Records, 1876-2012
    This subseries is arranged chronologically.
  - Subseries B. Special Students, Programs, And Fellowships, 1912-2016
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by file title.
  - Subseries C. Miscellaneous Files, 1867-2003
- Series II. Administrative Records, (79 boxes)
Container List
- Series I. Student Records, 1867-2016; (920 boxes) [RESTRICTED]
  - Series I. General Records, 1876-2012
    - Certificates and testimonials, 1876-1886 (Box 589)
    - Certificates and testimonials, 1885-1890 (Box 543)
    - Certificates and testimonials, 1889-1894 (Box 564)
    - Certificates and testimonials, 1891-1894 (Box 548)
    - Certificates and testimonials, 1894-1897 (Box 543)
    - Certificates and testimonials, 1895-1897 (Box 550)
    - Certificates and testimonials, 1897-1898 (Box 542)
    - Certificates and testimonials, 1899-1900 (Box 561)
    - Certificates and testimonials, 1901 (Box 586)
    - Certificates and testimonials, 1902 (Box 591)
    - Certificates and testimonials, 1903 (Box 594)
    - Certificates and testimonials, 1904 (Box 558)
    - Certificates and testimonials, 1905 (Box 597)
    - Certificates and testimonials, 1906 (Box 549)
    - Certificates and testimonials - Withdrawn, 1906-1910 (Box 599)
    - Certificates and testimonials, 1907 (Box 593)
    - Certificates and testimonials - Withdrawn, 1907 (Box 593)
    - Certificates and testimonials, 1908 (Box 568)
    - Certificates and testimonials, 1909 (Box 562)
    - Certificates and testimonials - Withdrawn, 1909-1910 (Box 562)
    - Certificates and testimonials, A-O, 1910 (Box 574)
    - Certificates and testimonials, P-Z, 1910 (Box 584)
    - Certificates and testimonials, 1911 (Box 563)
    - Certificates and testimonials, 1912 (Box 566)
    - Certificates and testimonials - Withdrawn, 1913 (Box 588)
    - Certificates and testimonials - Withdrawn, D-Irw, 1913-1917 (Box 577)
    - Certificates and testimonials - Withdrawn, J-M, 1913-1917 (Box 546)
    - Certificates and testimonials - Withdrawn, N-R, 1913-1917 (Box 554)
    - Certificates and testimonials - Withdrawn, S-Z, 1913-1917 (Box 560)
    - Certificates and testimonials, A-L, 1914 (Box 571)
    - Withdrawn, A-Z, 1914 (Box 650)
    - Certificates and testimonials - Withdrawn Exam Papers, 1914-1916 (Box 571)
    - Certificates and testimonials, 1915 (Box 573)
    - Certificates and testimonials, A-K, 1918 (Box 565)
    - Certificates and testimonials, A-K, 1919 (Box 178)
    - Certificates and testimonials, L-Z, 1919 (Box 656)
    - Certificates and testimonials, A-H, 1920 (Box 572)
    - Certificates and testimonials, J-W, 1920 (Box 17)
    - Withdrawn, A-W, 1920 (Box 18)
    - Regular, A-G, 1921 (Box 655)
    - Regular, G-R, 1921 (Box 583)
    - Regular, S-W, 1921 (Box 580)
    - Withdrawn, 1921 (Box 567)
    - Certificates and testimonials, A-H, 1922 (Box 579)
    - Withdrawn, A-H, M, 1922 (Box 654)
    - Withdrawn, N-Z, 1922 (Box 653)
    - Regular, A-F, 1923 (Box 582)
    - Regular, F-P, 1923 (Box 585)
    - Regular, R-Z, 1923 (Box 541)
    - Withdrawn, A-W, 1923 (Box 9)
    - Regular, A-D, 1924 (Box 14)
    - Regular, Duf-Joh, 1924 (Box 23)
    - Regular, Kel-Plat, 1924 (Box 24)
    - Regular, Pol-You, 1924 (Box 33)
    - Withdrawn, Abo-Ham, 1924 (Box 34)
    - Withdrawn, Her-Whi, 1924 (Box 43)
    - Regular, A-Ga, 1925 (Box 44)
    - Regular, Hi-Mcc, 1925 (Box 50)
    - Regular, M-Sm, 1925 (Box 19)
    - Regular, Sta-Z, 1925 (Box 11)
    - Withdrawn, Bai-Rey, 1925 (Box 51)
    - Withdrawn, R-W, 1925 (Box 56)
    - Regular, A-E, 1926 (Box 134)
    - Regular, E-K, 1926 (Box 135)
    - Regular, M-S, 1926 (Box 152)
    - Regular, S-Whi, 1926 (Box 153)
    - Withdrawn, A-H, 1926 (Box 153)
    - Withdrawn, Joh-Way, 1926 (Box 56)
    - Regular, Add-Gar, 1927 (Box 62)
    - Regular, Gib-Lew, 1927 (Box 63)
    - Regular, Nev-Whe, 1927 (Box 80)
    - Regular, W-Z, 1927 (Box 81)
    - Withdrawn, Abel-San, 1927 (Box 81)
    - Regular, Adl-Lad, 1928 (Box 99)
    - Regular, Leip-Rich, 1928 (Box 98)
    - Regular, S-Z, 1928 (Box 116)
    - Withdrawn, A-B, 1928 (Box 116)
    - Withdrawn, Big-Zim, 1928 (Box 117)
    - Regular, A-F, M-P, 1929 (Box 136)
    - Regular, G-M, 1929 (Box 137)
    - Regular, R-Z, 1929 (Box 154)
    - Withdrawn, A-S, 1929 (Box 155)
    - Withdrawn, W-Z, 1929 (Box 154)
    - Regular, A-E, 1930 (Box 65)
    - Regular, F-K, 1930 (Box 64)
    - Regular, L-W, 1930 (Box 100)
    - Withdrawn, A-D, S-W, 1930 (Box 10)
    - Withdrawn, Em-Smi, 1930 (Box 4)
    - Regular, Baktogas, 1931 (Box 82)
    - Regular, Gib-Joh, 1931 (Box 83)
    - Regular, Kea-Rob, 1931 (Box 118)
    - Withdrawn, Bal-Bren, 1931 (Box 100)
    - Withdrawn, Cook-Rud, 1931 (Box 101)
    - Withdrawn, S-Z, 1931 (Box 119)
    - Regular, A-C, 1932 (Box 138)
    - Regular, E-K, 1932 (Box 139)
    - Regular, L-R, 1932 (Box 156)
    - Regular, S-W, 1932 (Box 157)
    - Withdrawn, Ada-Rus, 1932 (Box 67)
    - Withdrawn, S-W, 1932 (Box 66)
    - Regular, A-Dun, 1933 (Box 525)
    - Regular, El-Hyd, 1933 (Box 528)
    - Regular, Jac-Roz, 1933 (Box 524)
    - Regular, Ru-Zel, 1933 (Box 527)
    - Withdrawn, A-K, 1933 (Box 66)
    - Regular, A-D, 1934 (Box 660)
    - Regular, F-J, 1934 (Box 540)
    - Regular, K-L, S-Z, 1934 (Box 54)
    - Regular, Lee-St, 1934 (Box 48)
    - Withdrawn, A-M, W-Z, 1934 (Box 55)
    - Withdrawn, Em-Smi, 1934 (Box 5)
    - Regular, A-F, 1935 (Box 6)
    - Regular, Fra-L, 1935 (Box 12)
    - Regular, M-R, 1935 (Box 22)
    - Regular, S-Z, 1935 (Box 21)
    - Withdrawn, A-J, 1935 (Box 32)
    - Withdrawn, K-Y, 1935 (Box 41)
    - Regular, A-D, 1936 (Box 42)
    - Regular, E-J, 1936 (Box 49)
    - Regular, K-Q, 1936 (Box 78)
    - Regular, R-Y, 1936 (Box 79)
    - Withdrawn, A-H, 1936 (Box 96)
    - Withdrawn, I-W, 1936 (Box 97)
    - Regular, A-C, 1937 (Box 133)
    - Regular, D-J, 1937 (Box 132)
    - Regular, K-R, 1937 (Box 57)
    - Regular, S-Z, 1937 (Box 7)
    - Withdrawn, A-H, 1937 (Box 114)
    - Withdrawn, J-Z, 1937 (Box 115)
    - Regular, A-E, 1938 (Box 25)
    - Regular, F-K, 1938 (Box 16)
    - Regular, L-Spa, 1938 (Box 26)
    - Regular, Spl-Z, 1938 (Box 35)
    - Withdrawn, A-Hix, 1938 (Box 76)
    - Withdrawn, Hil-W, 1938 (Box 15)
    - Regular, A-Coo, 1939 (Box 84)
    - Regular, Cra-Hays, 1939 (Box 85)
    - Regular, Jon-Muir, 1939 (Box 103)
    - Regular, Nel-Tri, 1939 (Box 102)
    - Regular, V-Z, 1939 (Box 120)
    - Withdrawn, Adams-Ham, 1939 (Box 120)
    - Withdrawn, Hec-Wyckoff, 1939 (Box 121)
    - Regular, B-C, 1940 (Box 141)
    - Regular, D-G, 1940 (Box 140)
    - Regular, H-M, 1940 (Box 158)
    - Regular, M-P, 1940 (Box 159)
    - Regular, Qui-Thor, 1940 (Box 86)
    - Regular, Tiet-Ziem, 1940 (Box 87)
    - Withdrawn, A-K, 1940 (Box 69)
    - Withdrawn, L-W, 1940 (Box 68)
    - Regular, A-Knox, Sch-Sy, 1941 (Box 105)
    - Regular, Kog-Ros, 1941 (Box 104)
    - Regular, T-Z, 1941 (Box 123)
    - Withdrawn, A-R, 1941 (Box 122)
    - Withdrawn, Ram-Zim, 1941 (Box 123)
    - Regular, B-G, 1942 (Box 143)
    - Regular, H-M, 1942 (Box 142)
    - Regular, R-Z, withdrawn, A-C, 1942 (Box 161)
    - Withdrawn, C-Z, 1942 (Box 160)
    - Regular, A-Ega, 1943 (Box 70)
    - Regular, Ell-L, 1943 (Box 71)
    - Regular, M-War, 1943 (Box 88)
    - Regular, Whe-Yas, 1943 (Box 89)
    - Withdrawn, All-West, 1943 (Box 89)
    - Withdrawn, Nay-Wilson, 1943 (Box 106)
    - Withdrawn, B-W, 1943-1945 (Box 149)
    - Regular, A-God, Mcr-Mur, 1944 (Box 125)
    - Regular, G-M, 1944 (Box 162)
    - Regular, N-T, 1944 (Box 144)
    - Regular, T-Z, 1944 (Box 145)
    - Withdrawn, Alb-Hine, 1944 (Box 106)
    - Withdrawn, Holt-Wright, 1944 (Box 107)
    - Class of 1945-4, withdrawn, A-H (Box 90)
    - Class of 1945-4, withdrawn, Har-Y (Box 91)
    - Regular, Abe-Bre, 1945 (Box 108)
    - Regular, Gre-Lynch, 1945 (Box 109)
    - Regular, Mee-Sche, 1945 (Box 72)
    - Regular, Schu-Woo, 1945 (Box 73)
    - Withdrawn, A-L, 1945 (Box 127)
    - Withdrawn, M-W, 1945 (Box 126)
    - Regular, A-F, 1946 (Box 164)
    - Regular, F-J, 1946 (Box 165)
    - Regular, L-S, 1946 (Box 147)
    - Regular, S-Z, 1946 (Box 146)
    - Withdrawn, M-W, 1946 (Box 126)
    - Regular, Aus-Hin, 1947 (Box 74)
    - Regular, Hir-Rux, 1947 (Box 75)
    - Regular, Sac-You, 1947 (Box 227)
    - Withdrawn, Alt-Gar, 1947 (Box 227)
    - Withdrawn, Han-Zis, 1947 (Box 196)
    - Regular, Aan-Rice, 1948 (Box 110)
    - Regular, Rood-Wright, 1948 (Box 111)
    - Withdrawn, Abreu-Gjer, 1948 (Box 111)
    - Withdrawn, H-Z, 1948 (Box 148)
    - Regular, Aber-Jef, 1949 (Box 128)
    - Regular, Joh-Swet, 1949 (Box 129)
    - Regular, T-Z, 1949 (Box 148)
    - Regular, B-C, 1950 (Box 167)
    - Regular, D-M, 1950 (Box 166)
    - Regular, Mis-Ste, 1950 (Box 77)
    - Regular, Ste-Z, 1950 (Box 95)
    - Withdrawn, A-Hur, 1950 (Box 8)
    - Withdrawn, I-Spe, 1950 (Box 95)
    - Regular, A-Den, 1951 (Box 112)
    - Regular, Dev-J, 1951 (Box 113)
    - Regular, K-Rob, 1951 (Box 131)
    - Regular, Rog-Z, 1951 (Box 130)
    - Withdrawn, A-Fre, 1951 (Box 130)
    - Withdrawn, How-Zah, 1951 (Box 94)
    - Regular, B-H, 1952 (Box 150)
    - Regular, H-R, 1952 (Box 151)
    - Regular, S-Z, 1952 (Box 168)
    - Withdrawn, A-K, 1952 (Box 168)
    - Withdrawn, K-Y, 1952 (Box 169)
    - Regular, Fla-Lind, 1953 (Box 170)
    - Regular, Llp-Ryan, 1953 (Box 171)
    - Regular, Sam-Zier, 1953 (Box 190)
    - Withdrawn, H-P, 1953 (Box 190)
    - Withdrawn, Pre-Y, 1953 (Box 189)
    - Regular, Ack-Jones, 1954 (Box 197)
    - Regular, Jud-Z, 1954 (Box 198)
    - Withdrawn, All-Wus, 1954 (Box 223)
    - Withdrawn, Kab-Rya, 1954-1970 (Box 3)
    - Withdrawn, Sto-Zro, 1954-1970 (Box 36)
    - Regular, Ab-Lev, 1955 (Box 240)
    - Regular, Agn-Che, 1955 (Box 52)
    - Regular, Lieb-Z, 1955 (Box 224)
    - Withdrawn, Ack-Z, 1955 (Box 241)
    - Regular, A-Ham, 1956 (Box 192)
    - Regular, H-Z, 1956 (Box 226)
    - Withdrawn, Aik-Wrigh, 1956 (Box 193)
    - Regular, Ack-Hor, 1957 (Box 172)
    - Regular, Hor-Rus, 1957 (Box 173)
    - Regular, Saf-Yan, 1957 (Box 199)
    - Withdrawn, Aba-Gol, 1957 (Box 199)
    - Withdrawn, Gor-Woo, 1957 (Box 200)
    - Regular, A-Hol, 1958 (Box 194)
    - Regular, H-O, 1958 (Box 225)
    - Regular, P-Z, 1958 (Box 520)
    - Withdrawn, A-Hal, 1958 (Box 520)
    - Withdrawn, Hya-Zor, 1958 (Box 521)
    - Regular, Ack-Lar, 1959 (Box 255)
    - Regular, Law-Zalk, 1959 (Box 256)
    - Withdrawn, Alsc-Latt, 1959 (Box 174)
    - Withdrawn, Lee-Youn, 1959 (Box 175)
    - Regular, Hun-Mar, 1960 (Box 40)
    - Withdrawn, A-Z, 1960 (Box 519)
    - Withdrawn, K-Y, 1960 (Box 20)
    - Regular, Fle-Jun, 1961 (Box 45)
    - Regular, Kar-Men, 1961 (Box 46)
    - Regular, Mer-Rub, 1961 (Box 60)
    - Regular, Rub-Wil, 1961 (Box 61)
    - Withdrawn, Adam-Kos, 1961 (Box 522)
    - Withdrawn, Ald-Joh, 1961 (Box 59)
    - Withdrawn, Kah-Yur, 1961 (Box 58)
    - Withdrawn, Kres-Zim, 1961 (Box 523)
    - Regular, A-J, 1962 (Box 176)
    - Regular, K-S, 1962 (Box 177)
    - Regular, T-Z, 1962 (Box 203)
    - Withdrawn, A-Mic, 1962 (Box 203)
    - Withdrawn, Mil-Wy, 1962 (Box 204)
    - Regular, A-Hug, 1963 (Box 214)
    - Regular, Hur-P, 1963 (Box 213)
    - Regular, R-Z, 1963 (Box 228)
    - Withdrawn, A-Gre, 1963 (Box 228)
    - Withdrawn, Gri-W, 1963 (Box 229)
    - Regular, A-H, 1964 (Box 47)
    - Regular, Mat-She, 1964 (Box 30)
    - Regular, Sch-Wen, 1964 (Box 39)
    - Regular, Wic-Z, 1964 (Box 29)
    - Withdrawn, A-K, 1964 (Box 29)
    - Regular, Che-Fitz, 1965 (Box 53)
    - Regular, Wil-Zio, 1965 (Box 532)
    - Withdrawn, Ama-Knif, 1965 (Box 532)
    - Regular, Ada-Cob, 1966 (Box 205)
    - Regular, Coc-Fit, 1966 (Box 526)
    - Regular, Fla-Hol, 1966 (Box 215)
    - Regular, Hor-Lip, 1966 (Box 230)
    - Regular, Lis-Rut, 1966 (Box 244)
    - Regular, Sal-Vau, 1966 (Box 231)
    - Regular, Vin-Zoe, 1966 (Box 529)
    - Withdrawn, A-Good, 1966 (Box 529)
    - Withdrawn, Han-Z, 1966 (Box 246)
    - Regular, A-C, 1967 (Box 259)
    - Regular, D-F, 1967 (Box 247)
    - Regular, G-Hog, 1967 (Box 181)
    - Regular, Hol-K, 1967 (Box 260)
    - Regular, L-M, 1967 (Box 262)
    - Regular, N-P, 1967 (Box 183)
    - Regular, Sca-Tom, 1967 (Box 184)
    - Regular, Tra-W, 1967 (Box 210)
    - Withdrawn, A-Moo, 1967 (Box 531)
    - Withdrawn, Mur-Z, 1967 (Box 530)
    - Regular, A-Cha, 1968 (Box 245)
    - Regular, Chi-D, 1968 (Box 257)
    - Regular, E-Hel, 1968 (Box 179)
    - Regular, Hen-K, 1968 (Box 258)
    - Regular, Lab-Petr, 1968 (Box 180)
    - Regular, Pett-R, 1968 (Box 206)
    - Regular, S-Vai, 1968 (Box 216)
    - Regular, Van-Z, 1968 (Box 207)
    - Withdrawn, A-See, 1968 (Box 217)
    - Withdrawn, She-W, 1968 (Box 232)
    - Regular, A-Blai, 1969 (Box 182)
    - Regular, Blak-C, 1969 (Box 208)
    - Regular, D-F, 1969 (Box 209)
    - Regular, G-Hop, 1969 (Box 218)
    - Regular, Hud-K, 1969 (Box 233)
    - Regular, L-Pee, 1969 (Box 219)
    - Regular, Pel-Slo, 1969 (Box 234)
    - Regular, Sma-Whi, 1969 (Box 248)
    - Withdrawn, Kno-Wei, 1969 (Box 261)
    - Regular, A-Cat, 1970 (Box 235)
    - Regular, Cav-Eva, 1970 (Box 220)
    - Regular, Fau-Greg, 1970 (Box 249)
    - Regular, Gri-Kar, 1970 (Box 236)
    - Regular, Kel-Nev, 1970 (Box 250)
    - Regular, Nor-Rov, 1970 (Box 263)
    - Regular, Rub-Tor, 1970 (Box 264)
    - Regular, Wei-Z, 1970 (Box 185)
    - Withdrawn, Ash-Joh, 1970 (Box 211)
    - Withdrawn, Jol-Z, 1970 (Box 186)
    - Regular, Ads-Bre, 1971 (Box 391)
    - Regular, Bri-Dea, 1971 (Box 390)
    - Regular, Dec-Goo, 1971 (Box 398)
    - Regular, Gor-Hic, 1971 (Box 399)
    - Regular, Ho-Lie, 1971 (Box 408)
    - Regular, Lon-Moy, 1971 (Box 407)
    - Regular, Mui-San, 1971 (Box 414)
    - Regular, Sch-Smi, 1971 (Box 415)
    - Regular, Sol-Z, 1971 (Box 349)
    - Withdrawn, A-Hic, 1971 (Box 367)
    - Withdrawn, Hob-Pic, 1971 (Box 329)
    - Withdrawn, Pic-Vau, 1971 (Box 348)
    - Withdrawn, W, 1971 (Box 661)
    - Regular, Alk-Brc, 1972 (Box 251)
    - Regular, Bred-Cuc, 1972 (Box 237)
    - Regular, Dab-Gat, 1972 (Box 265)
    - Regular, Gel-Har, 1972 (Box 252)
    - Regular, Hau-Kim, 1972 (Box 187)
    - Regular, Kim-Lyd, 1972 (Box 266)
    - Regular, Mac-Nun, 1972 (Box 222)
    - Regular, Off-Rut, 1972 (Box 188)
    - Regular, Sam-Sut, 1972 (Box 221)
    - Regular, Tap-Wil, 1972 (Box 212)
    - Regular, Win-York, 1972 (Box 533)
    - Withdrawn, Al-Kirk, 1972 (Box 533)
    - Withdrawn, Kra-Smi, 1972 (Box 269)
    - Withdrawn, Snyd-Youn, 1972 (Box 534)
    - Regular, Acu-Bur, 1973 (Box 381)
    - Regular, Bur-Cur, 1973 (Box 382)
    - Regular, Dal-Gab, 1973 (Box 388)
    - Regular, Gil-Hoo, 1973 (Box 389)
    - Regular, Hor-Kuh, 1973 (Box 393)
    - Regular, Lai-Mil, 1973 (Box 392)
    - Regular, Mor-Ple, 1973 (Box 400)
    - Regular, Plu-Rol, 1973 (Box 401)
    - Regular, Sab-Simon, 1973 (Box 535)
    - Regular, Simo-Vola, 1973 (Box 285)
    - Regular, Wal-Zip, 1973 (Box 536)
    - Withdrawn, A-Bro, 1973 (Box 536)
    - Withdrawn, Evans-John, 1973 (Box 321)
    - Withdrawn, Mad-Will, 1973 (Box 322)
    - Regular, Ald-Cob, 1974 (Box 286)
    - Regular, Cog-Furt, 1974 (Box 270)
    - Regular, Gab-Jac, 1974 (Box 287)
    - Regular, Jac-Mar, 1974 (Box 303)
    - Regular, Mas-Plap, 1974 (Box 323)
    - Regular, Plat-Shob, 1974 (Box 304)
    - Regular, Sil-Urg, 1974 (Box 342)
    - Regular, Van-Zor, 1974 (Box 324)
    - Withdrawn, A-J, 1974 (Box 658)
    - Withdrawn, K-Z, 1974 (Box 659)
    - Regular, A-Cox, 1975 (Box 238)
    - Regular, Cox-Fox, 1975 (Box 239)
    - Regular, Fra-Hog, 1975 (Box 253)
    - Regular, Hol-Law, 1975 (Box 254)
    - Regular, Lei-Obri, 1975 (Box 267)
    - Regular, Och-Robe, 1975 (Box 268)
    - Regular, Rug-Val, 1975 (Box 341)
    - Regular, Vau-Zu, 1975 (Box 340)
    - Withdrawn, A-Jos, 1975 (Box 537)
    - Withdrawn, Kap-Mos, 1975 (Box 360)
    - Withdrawn, Nal-Zim, 1975 (Box 538)
    - Regular, Aba-Chl, 1976 (Box 361)
    - Regular, Chr-Evan, 1976 (Box 343)
    - Regular, Fag-Hag, 1976 (Box 271)
    - Regular, Hal-Jag, 1976 (Box 362)
    - Regular, Kae-Mann, 1976 (Box 288)
    - Regular, Mans-Out, 1976 (Box 272)
    - Regular, Pac-Rus, 1976 (Box 289)
    - Regular, Sam-Swi, 1976 (Box 305)
    - Regular, Tal-Zoe, 1976 (Box 306)
    - Withdrawn, Adl-Fur, 1976 (Box 539)
    - Withdrawn, Gei-Rai, 1976 (Box 325)
    - Withdrawn, Rap-Zis, 1976 (Box 344)
    - Regular, Abe-Cas, 1977 (Box 316)
    - Regular, Cat-Fai, 1977 (Box 315)
    - Regular, Faw-Hay, 1977 (Box 298)
    - Regular, Hea-Kan, 1977 (Box 297)
    - Regular, Kay-Lin, 1977 (Box 279)
    - Regular, Lit-Ose, 1977 (Box 280)
    - Regular, Ost-Ros, 1977 (Box 334)
    - Regular, Rub-Sus, 1977 (Box 335)
    - Regular, Tab-Zei, 1977 (Box 354)
    - Regular, Zil, 1977 (Box 355)
    - Withdrawn, Abr-Gar, 1977 (Box 355)
    - Withdrawn, Gil-San, 1977 (Box 373)
    - Withdrawn, Sar-Zil, 1977 (Box 374)
    - Regular, Abr-Cah, 1978 (Box 345)
    - Regular, Cal-Fit, 1978 (Box 363)
    - Regular, Fri-Han, 1978 (Box 273)
    - Regular, Har-Kra, 1978 (Box 364)
    - Regular, Kog-Moo, 1978 (Box 274)
    - Regular, Mor-Rap, 1978 (Box 290)
    - Regular, Red-Sil, 1978 (Box 372)
    - Regular, Sin-Vos, 1978 (Box 371)
    - Regular, Wad-Zim, 1978 (Box 353)
    - Withdrawn, Abr-Car, 1978 (Box 353)
    - Withdrawn, Car-Low, 1978 (Box 352)
    - Withdrawn, Man-Z, 1978 (Box 333)
    - Regular, Ach-Bro, 1979 (Box 281)
    - Regular, Bru-Dur, 1979 (Box 282)
    - Regular, Ebe-Gol, 1979 (Box 300)
    - Regular, Gol-Joh, 1979 (Box 299)
    - Regular, Joh-Lus, 1979 (Box 317)
    - Regular, Lyn-Mos, 1979 (Box 318)
    - Regular, Mou-Robinson, L., 1979 (Box 308)
    - Regular, Robinson, S.-Star, 1979 (Box 326)
    - Regular, Sri-Z, 1979 (Box 291)
    - Regular, Ste-Wright, 1979 (Box 307)
    - Withdrawn, A-Hui, 1979 (Box 291)
    - Withdrawn, Ing-Z, 1979 (Box 327)
    - Regular, A-Ber, 1980 (Box 314)
    - Regular, Bes-Cob, 1980 (Box 332)
    - Regular, Coh-Fit, 1980 (Box 296)
    - Regular, Flo-Hau, 1980 (Box 313)
    - Regular, Hay-Lap, 1980 (Box 278)
    - Regular, Lau-Mel, 1980 (Box 295)
    - Regular, Mes-Pie, 1980 (Box 336)
    - Regular, Pol-Ryd, 1980 (Box 337)
    - Regular, Sab-Tro, 1980 (Box 356)
    - Regular, Tro-Zem, 1980 (Box 357)
    - Withdrawn, Alb-Eme, 1980 (Box 376)
    - Withdrawn, Fox-Zez, 1980 (Box 375)
    - Regular, A-Buc, 1981 (Box 346)
    - Regular, Bul-Cun, 1981 (Box 347)
    - Regular, Dal-Fro, 1981 (Box 366)
    - Regular, Gae-Hun, 1981 (Box 365)
    - Regular, Jac-Leu, 1981 (Box 370)
    - Regular, Lev-Mor, 1981 (Box 277)
    - Regular, Nat-Pow, 1981 (Box 369)
    - Regular, Pra-Sem, 1981 (Box 351)
    - Regular, Sco-Tob, 1981 (Box 284)
    - Regular, Tod-Zuk, 1981 (Box 283)
    - Withdrawn, Acc-Nei, 1981 (Box 301)
    - Withdrawn, Ng-Zil, 1981 (Box 302)
    - Regular, A-Cal, 1982 (Box 292)
    - Regular, Cam-Don, 1982 (Box 309)
    - Regular, Dor-Fre, 1982 (Box 310)
    - Regular, Frey-Hel, 1982 (Box 328)
    - Regular, Her-Kno, 1982 (Box 330)
    - Regular, Koh-Mar, 1982 (Box 331)
    - Regular, Mar-O'cc, 1982 (Box 311)
    - Regular, O'co-Rus, 1982 (Box 312)
    - Regular, Sab-Spe, 1982 (Box 293)
    - Regular, Spi-Von, 1982 (Box 294)
    - Regular, Wak-Z, 1982 (Box 275)
    - Withdrawn, A-Fer, 1982 (Box 275)
    - Withdrawn, Fra-May, 1982 (Box 276)
    - Withdrawn, Mch-Z, 1982 (Box 368)
    - Regular, Ack-Cal, 1983 (Box 386)
    - Regular, Cal-Cur, 1983 (Box 387)
    - Regular, Ded-Fon, 1983 (Box 380)
    - Regular, Fox-Hun, 1983 (Box 379)
    - Regular, Hur-Kar, 1983 (Box 377)
    - Regular, Kru-Lwin, 1983 (Box 378)
    - Regular, Mar-Orl, 1983 (Box 359)
    - Regular, Oro-Riv, 1983 (Box 358)
    - Regular, Rob-Sei, 1983 (Box 339)
    - Regular, Ser-Tho, 1983 (Box 338)
    - Regular, Tho-Wit, 1983 (Box 320)
    - Regular, Wit-Zuc, 1983 (Box 319)
    - Withdrawn, Ami-Kin, 1983 (Box 319)
    - Withdrawn, Knox-Wood, 1983 (Box 350)
    - Withdrawn, S-Z, 1983 (Box 21)
    - Regular, Aar-Bur, 1984 (Box 409)
    - Regular, Bur-Dii, 1984 (Box 410)
    - Regular, Dod-Fry, 1984 (Box 402)
    - Regular, Fun-Han, 1984 (Box 403)
    - Regular, Har-Kal, 1984 (Box 394)
    - Regular, Kap-Lyo, 1984 (Box 395)
    - Regular, Mac-Noo, 1984 (Box 422)
    - Regular, Nov-Roc, 1984 (Box 406)
    - Regular, Rog-Spa, 1984 (Box 413)
    - Regular, Spe-Was, 1984 (Box 421)
    - Regular, Wea-Z, 1984 (Box 416)
    - Withdrawn, A-Coo, 1984 (Box 416)
    - Withdrawn, Cur-Mcg, 1984 (Box 420)
    - Withdrawn, Mil-Wri, 1984 (Box 31)
    - Regular, Ab-Bro, 1985 (Box 419)
    - Regular, Bro-Dow, 1985 (Box 384)
    - Regular, Doy-Gor, 1985 (Box 383)
    - Regular, Got-Hol, 1985 (Box 404)
    - Regular, Hol-Lew, 1985 (Box 385)
    - Regular, Lew-Mor, 1985 (Box 418)
    - Regular, Mos-Rov, 1985 (Box 405)
    - Regular, Rub-Tay, 1985 (Box 417)
    - Regular, Ter-Zam, 1985 (Box 411)
    - Withdrawn, Aco-Pir, 1985 (Box 396)
    - Withdrawn, Pop-Zar, 1985 (Box 412)
    - Regular, Abb-Bri, 1986 (Box 467)
    - Regular, Bru-Dav, 1986 (Box 468)
    - Regular, Dav-Gad, 1986 (Box 426)
    - Regular, Gaf-Hod, 1986 (Box 427)
    - Regular, Greenb-Kalt, 1986 (Box 431)
    - Regular, Hoo-Lin, 1986 (Box 435)
    - Regular, Lis-Mor, 1986 (Box 436)
    - Regular, Mue-Rob, 1986 (Box 443)
    - Regular, Robi-Smith, 1986 (Box 444)
    - Regular, Smith, K-Wid, 1986 (Box 451)
    - Regular, Wie-Zuc, 1986 (Box 452)
    - Withdrawn, A-Fine, 1986 (Box 452)
    - Withdrawn, Fit-Qui, 1986 (Box 459)
    - Withdrawn, Ric-Zie, 1986 (Box 460)
    - Regular, A-By, 1987 (Box 428)
    - Regular, Ca-Dav, 1987 (Box 429)
    - Regular, Day-Gie, 1987 (Box 437)
    - Regular, Gil-Hur, 1987 (Box 438)
    - Regular, Hus-Law, 1987 (Box 445)
    - Regular, Lee-Mor, 1987 (Box 446)
    - Regular, Mur-Red, 1987 (Box 453)
    - Regular, Rei-Smith, 1987 (Box 454)